Guide to the Jerome Ziegler papers, 1955-2011.
Ziegler, Jerome papers
- Series VIII. Interviews
  - Neil Sanders; Mr. Dickey; Peter Levene, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Chris Hayes; Jack Mansell; John Ray; Judith Ryder; Alan Little, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Morris Kaufman, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Uri Aviram, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Henry Ricciuti, no date (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Series IX. Calendars, Job Corps Records
  - Daily Calendars, 1972-2012 (Box 9)
  - Passports (Box 9)
  - Scrapbooks - Rodman Job Corps Center- Jerome Ziegler was the First Director, 1965-1968 (Box 9)
  - Job Corps Newsletters, Publications, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Job Corps Scrapbook, 1966-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Job Corps 30th Anniversary (1995); Alumni Booklet (1989) (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Series X. Warren Ziegler Files (Jerome Ziegler's Brother)
  - Warren Ziegler's Publications, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - The Futures-Invention Associates Reports, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - The Futures-Invention Associates Publications, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - "The Tao of Spirit", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - The Futures-Invention Associates Reports and Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 8, Folder 30)